Guide to the Rice University KTRU Radio records, 1962-2018 UA 011
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series I: Audio recordings, 1968-2007, 59004
  - Sub-Series: 1984/1985, 59452
    - Chicken Skin Music - Mike Mandrell and John Campbell, 1984-09-19; wrc07502 (Box 19)
      Contents include: On "Chicken Skin Music," Mike Mandrell and John Campbell perform. Speakers: Mike Mandrell, John Campbell, David John Scribner
    - R.E.M. interview, 1984-09-19; wrc07443 (Box 19)
      Contents include: Ray Isle and David-John Scribner interview Peter Buck of R.E.M. They discuss music in Georgia, musical influences, composing, songwriting, and their show at Numbers. Recording ends abruptly. Speakers: Peter Buck, Ray Isle, David-John Scribner
    - The Dishes interview, 1984-09-20; wrc07444 (Box 19)
      Contents include: Mike Scott interviews Jimmy Raycraft and Dickie Malone about their current music and previous bands. Speakers: Jimmy Raycraft, Dickie Malone, Mike Scott
    - To the Point - Elizabeth Long, 1984-09-25; wrc07445 (Box 19)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Roger Gray talks to Dr. Elizabeth Long about physical and sexual abuse within families. Speakers: Elizabeth Long, Roger Gray
    - To the Point - Francis Loewenheim, 1984-10-01; wrc07446 (Box 19)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Roger Gray talks to Dr. Francis Loewenheim about presidential debates and how they inform the public. Speakers: Francis Loewenheim, Roger Gray
    - John Irving reading, 1984-10-05; wrc07447 (Box 19)
      Contents include: Delete beginning of dead air. John Irving describing and reading from "The Cider House Rules" at the Grand Hall at the Rice Memorial Center. Speakers: John Irving
    - To the Point - Gilbert Cuthbertson, 1984-10-08; wrc07448 (Box 19)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Roger Gray talks to Dr. Gilbert Cuthbertson about the Texas U.S. Senate race between Lloyd Doggett and Lindsey Graham. Speakers: Gilbert Cuthbertson, Roger Gray
    - To the Point - Niels Nielsen, 1984-10-15; wrc07449 (Box 19)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Roger Gray talks to Dr. Niels Nielsen about the influence of religion on politics. Speakers: Niels Nielsen, Roger Gray
    - To the Point - Francis Loewenheim, 1984-10-22; wrc07450 (Box 19)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Roger Gray talks to Dr. Francis Loewenheim about U.S. and Russian negotiations and disarmament. Speakers: Francis Loewenheim, Roger Gray
    - To the Point - Chandler Davidson, 1984-10-29; wrc07451 (Box 19)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Roger Gray talks to Dr. Chandler Davidson about political party drift. Speakers: Chandler Davidson, Roger Gray
    - News Archive 2, 1984-1985; wrc07486 (Box 19)
      Contents include: (00:01) Rep. Michael A. Andrews election report; (00:41) Lloyd Doggett concession report; (01:47) Dr. Falk [?] on being in Haiti, blankets for Haiti; (08:06) Sports review/preview. Speakers: Henry De La Garza, Arthur Rabeau
    - To the Point - Stephen Klineberg, 1984-11-05; wrc07452 (Box 19)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Roger Gray talks to Dr. Stephen Klineberg about the Houston Survey, part 1. Speakers: Stephen Klineberg, Roger Gray
    - To the Point - Stephen Klineberg, 1984-11-12; wrc07453 (Box 19)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Roger Gray talks to Dr. Stephen Klineberg about the Houston Survey, part 2. Speakers: Stephen Klineberg, Roger Gray
    - To the Point - Briance Mascarenhas, 1984-11-26; wrc07454 (Box 19)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Roger Gray talks to Dr. Briance Mascarenhas about profits in the oil industry during the boom. Speakers: Briance Mascarenhas, Roger Gray
    - To the Point - Niels Nielsen, 1984-12-03; wrc07455 (Box 19)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Roger Gray talks to Dr. Niels Nielsen about the influence of religion in politics. Speakers: Niels Nielsen, Roger Gray
    - To the Point - Ewa Thompson, 1984-12-10; wrc07456 (Box 19)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Roger Gray talks to Dr. Ewa Thompson on Humanities education, part 1. Speakers: Ewa Thompson, Roger Gray
    - To the Point - Ewa Thompson, 1984-12-10; wrc07457 (Box 19)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Roger Gray talks to Dr. Ewa Thompson on Humanities education, part 2. Speakers: Ewa Thompson, Roger Gray
    - To the Point - C. R. O'Dell, 1984-12-24; wrc07458 (Box 19)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Roger Gray talks to Dr. C. R. O'Dell about Halley's Comet. Speakers: C. R. O'Dell, Roger Gray
    - Modern English interview, 1984; wrc07958 (Box 19)
      Contents include: Stan Barber interviews Gary McDowell about touring Texas and new music. McDowell does a station ID. Speakers: Gary McDowell, Stan Barber
    - The Bongos interview, 1984; wrc07978 (Box 19)
      Contents include: A KTRU DJ interviews Rob Norris of The Bongos about their influences, working with Richard Gottehrer, "Drums Along the Hudson," solo records, Mitch Easter, touring, and working with RCA. They do a station ID. Speakers: Rob Norris, Michael Zakes, Richard Barone, James Mastro
    - Charlie Pickett and The Eggs live, 1984; wrc08049 (Box 19)
      Contents include: Charlie Pickett and The Eggs live, location unknown. Speakers: Charlie Pickett, Dave Froshnider, John Galway, John Salton
    - News Archive 3, 1984-1985; wrc07487 (Box 19)
      Contents include: (00:01) Personality of the Week: Trevor Baxter; (13:40) Student Association president elections and speeches; (33:40) Personality of the Week: George Rupp appointed university president; (44:14) Houston Grand Opera's "The Magic Flute" review. Speakers: Trevor Baxter, Jana Sanchez, Darryl Burke, Barry Nicholson, Tracy Winn, Neal Quimby, George Rupp, Irv Cutter
    - To the Point - John Adams, 1985-01-14; wrc07459 (Box 19)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Roger Gray talks to Dr. John Adams about the declining price of oil. Speakers: John Adams, Roger Gray
    - Affirmative Action debate, 1985-01-17; wrc07460 (Box 19)
      Contents include: The Project 91.7 Affirmative Action Debate features moderator David Phillips. On the for side, George Greanias and Bill Oliver are matched against John Goodner and Albert Walling. This debate took place a few days before a Houston referendum on adding the phrase "sexual orientation" to a non-discrimination ordinance. Stan Barber, Jeff Mathews and Mike Gladu produced the debate. Speakers: David Phillips, George Greanias, Bill Oliver, John Goodner, Albert Walling
    - To the Point - Stephen Klineberg, 1985-01-21; wrc07461 (Box 19)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Roger Gray talks to Dr. Stephen Klineberg about the Houston Survey results based on age. Speakers: Stephen Klineberg, Roger Gray
    - William F. Buckley, Jr. speech, 1985-01-25; wrc07462 (Box 19)
      Contents include: William F. Buckley, Jr. speaks at the Grand Hall in the Rice Memorial Center as part of the Rice Institute for Policy Analysis dinner. He discusses temperament of the South, his critique of Rev. Jesse Jackson's assessment of Detroit, supply side economics, and discrimination. Speakers: William F. Buckley, Jr., Joseph Cooper
    - To the Point - Stephen Klineberg, 1985-01-28; wrc07463 (Box 19)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Roger Gray talks to Dr. Stephen Klineberg about the Houston Survey results based on gender. Speakers: Stephen Klineberg, Roger Gray
    - To the Point - John Boles, 1985-02-04; wrc07464 (Box 19)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Roger Gray talks to Dr. John Boles about the Journal of Southern History and the South. Speakers: John Boles, Roger Gray
    - To the Point - John Adams, 1985-02-11; wrc07465 (Box 19)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Roger Gray talks to Dr. John Adams about the theory of nuclear winter. Speakers: John Adams, Roger Gray
    - To the Point - Julia Ching, 1985-02-18; wrc07466 (Box 19)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Roger Gray talks to Dr. Julia Ching about the history of religion in China. Speakers: Julia Ching, Roger Gray
    - Preston Reed live, 1985-02-20; wrc07467 (Box 20)
      Contents include: Preston Reed plays live at Willy's Pub.
    - To the Point - Julia Ching, 1985-02-25; wrc07488 (Box 20)
    - To the Point - John Guilmartin, 1985-03-11; wrc07468 (Box 20)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Roger Gray talks to Dr. John Guilmartin about U.S. and Russian arms balance. Speakers: John Guilmartin, Roger Gray
    - John Giorno interview, 1985-03-15; wrc07469 (Box 20)
      Contents include: On "The S and M Show," a DJ talks to poet John Giorno about Patti Smith, dial-a-poem, poetry albums, Laurie Anderson, finances, living in New York, and touring. Speaker: John Giorno
    - To the Point - John Guilmartin, 1985-03-18; wrc07470 (Box 20)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Roger Gray talks to Dr. John Guilmartin about the past and future of the space shuttle. Speakers: John Guilmartin, Roger Gray
    - To the Point - Ibrahim Kamalud Din, 1985-03-25; wrc07471 (Box 20)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Roger Gray talks to Ibrahim Kamalud Din about history of Islam in the U.S. Speakers: Ibrahim Kamalud Din, Roger Gray
    - To the Point - Ibrahim Kamalud Din, 1985-04-01; wrc07472 (Box 20)
    - To the Point - Francis Loewenheim, 1985-04-08; wrc07473 (Box 20)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Roger Gray talks to Dr. Francis Loewenheim about the Yalta Conference. Speakers: Francis Loewenheim, Roger Gray
    - Beer Bike, 1985-04-13; wrc07474 (Box 20)
      Contents include: Jonathan Sadow and Mike Gladu provide play-by-play for the 1985 Beer Bike women's and men's races. Speakers: Jonathan Sadow, Mike Gladu
    - To the Point - Francis Loewenheim, 1985-04-15; wrc07475 (Box 20)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Roger Gray talks to Dr. Francis Loewenheim about Mikhaeil Gorbachev. Speakers: Francis Loewenheim, Roger Gray
    - Semi-Cute, 1985-04-21; wrc07476 (Box 20)
      Contents include: On "No One Expects," Jonathan Sadow's radio play "Semi-Cute" produced by Stan Barber. Speakers: Susan Buchanan, Cindy Smith, John Knapp, Stan Barber, George Webb, Patrick Dyson
    - To the Point - Don Benjamin, 1985-04-22; wrc07477 (Box 20)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Roger Gray talks to Dr. Don Benjamin about the Bible. Speakers: Don Benjamin, Roger Gray
    - To the Point - Don Benjamin, 1985-04-29; wrc07478 (Box 20)
    - To the Point - Stephen Klineberg, 1985-05-20; wrc07479 (Box 20)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Roger Gray talks to Dr. Stephen Klineberg about the Houston Survey and how it compares to other major cities. Speakers: Stephen Klineberg, Roger Gray
    - To the Point - Stephen Klineberg, 1985-05-27; wrc07480 (Box 20)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Roger Gray talks to Dr. Stephen Klineberg about the Houston Survey, Houston politics, and the sexual orientation referendum. Speakers: Stephen Klineberg, Roger Gray
    - To the Point - Werner Kelber, 1985-06-03; wrc07481 (Box 20)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Roger Gray talks to Dr. Werner Kelber about the biblical Gospels. Speakers: Werner Kelber, Roger Gray
    - To the Point - Werner Kelber, 1985-06-10; wrc07482 (Box 20)
    - To the Point - Chandler Davidson, 1985-06-17; wrc07483 (Box 20)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Roger Gray talks to Dr. Chandler Davidson about the No Pass No Play rule. Speakers: Chandler Davidson, Roger Gray
    - Bongos ID, 1985; wrc07957 (Box 20)
      Contents include: The band the Bongos do a station ID. Speakers: Richard Barone, Rob Norris, Frank Giannini, James Mastro
    - Jerry Jeff Walker PSAs, 1985; wrc07987 (Box 20)
      Contents include: Jerry Jeff Walker does five PSAs on school bus safety for the Texas State Department of Highways and Public Transportation. Speaker: Jerry Jeff Walker
    - Kate Bush ID, 1985; wrc08048 (Box 20)
      Contents include: Kate Bush does a station ID. Speaker: Kate Bush
  - Sub-Series: 1985/1986
    - To the Point - Frank Tittle, 1985-07-08; wrc07518 (Box 20)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Roger Gray talks to Dr. Frank Tittle about Pres. Ronald Reagan's Star Wars. Speakers: Frank Tittle, Roger Gray
    - To the Point - Jean Claude de Bremaecker, 1985-07-08; wrc07519 (Box 20)
      Contents include: On "To the Point," Roger Gray talks to Dr. Jean Claude de Bremaecker about the field of Geology and continental drift. Speakers: Jean Claude de Bremaecker, Roger Gray
    - Jonathan Richman interview, 1985-08-04; wrc07520 (Box 20)
      Contents include: Phil Calvin and Stu Gretchen talks to Jonathan Richman about his fan club, his concerts, touring, favorite music, writing songs for children, Native American politics. We deleted sections of dead air. Audio has issues. Speakers: Phil Calvin, Stu Gretchen, Jonathan Richman
    - University of the Damned promos, 1985-09; wrc07960 (Box 20)
      Contents include: Promos for the radio show "University of the Damned."
    - Chicken Skin Music, 1985-10-02; wrc07521 (Box 20)
      Contents include: Delete beginning. On "Chicken Skin Music," (00:01) Janice Rubin performs Yiddish folk music with Barry Roberts on guitar; (42:51) Mike Mandrell plays acoustic guitar; (01:06:21) Banded Geckos play. Speakers: Evelyne Taylor, Tim Taylor, David John Scribner, Janice Rubin, Barry Roberts, Mike Mandrell, John McNath
    - Up in the Air - George Rupp, 1985-10; wrc07959 (Box 20)
      Contents include: KTRU news reporters and Thresher writers interview soon-to-be inaugurated George Rupp about Fondren Library, creating connections between Rice and Houston, building a medical or law school, religion on campus, increasing Rice's recognition outside the southwest region, and improving food service. We deleted outtakes from another radio program. Speakers: Stan Barber, George Rupp, Henry De La Garza, Mark Nash, David Frezenheim, Jana Sanchez, Eric Salituro, David Friesenhahn
    - Chicken Skin Music - Bill Cade and Don Sanders, 1985-11-20; wrc07522 (Box 20)
      Contents include: On "Chicken Skin Music," (00:01) Bill Cade performs live; (33:48) Don Sanders performs live. Speakers: Don Sanders, Bill Cade, David John Scribner
    - KTRU Benefit, 1985-12-05; wrc07523 (Box 20)
      Contents include: KTRU Benefit held in the Grand Hall of the Rice Memorial Center. Performers: (00:01) The Bat Surfers; (33:52) The Footnotes; (01:47:48) Fab Motion. Speakers: Todd Leger, Toby Blunt
    - Rice Radio Journal - Nicaragua, 1985-00-00; wrc07992 (Box 20)
      Contents include: On "Rice Radio Journal," Jana Sanchez talks to Hugh Brantley about the U.S.'s support of terrorist forces in Nicaragua, history of U.S. involvement in Nicaragua, rule under Anastasio Somoza Debayle vs. Sandinistas, Iran-contra Affair, Soviet influence, and trade. Speakers: Hugh Brantley, Jana Sanchez
    - Fab Motion interview, 1986-02-16; wrc07524 (Box 20)
      Contents include: Alex Malinin interviews members of Fab Motion, Todd Leger, Toby Blunt, Kim Hickman, and Clint Davidson about their music influences, live performances, press, and advice to other bands. Includes a station ID. Speakers: Todd Leger, Toby Blunt, Kim Hickman, Clint Davidson, Alex Malinin
    - Texas Music Special 1, 1986-02-22; wrc07525 (Box 20)
      Contents include: (00:01) True Believers; (14:08) The Windows; (29:22) Fab Motion. This program features short interviews, history on the bands, and music. Speakers: Alejandro Escovedo, Javier, Escovedo, Jon Dee Graham, Denny DeGorio, Kevin Foley, Tom Harvey, Frank Brothers, David Highfill, Toby Blunt, Todd Leger, Kim Hickman, Clint Davidson, Alex Malinin
    - Student Association President interviews, 1986-02-23; wrc07526 (Box 20)
      Contents include: A KTRU DJ interviews students, Dan Price, Carol Drummond, and Tom Perrault, running for the position of Student Association President. Speakers: Dan Price, Carol Drummond, Tom Perrault
    - Various KTRU Interviews, 1986-02; wrc07484 (Box 21)
      Contents include: (00:01) Members of The Wolves, Larry Selman and Mike Swann discuss how the band formed, recording, their families, and songwriting; (19:48) Members of Living Pieces, Noel Flatt, Karen Bice, and Peter Freimanis discuss songwriting, their music video, the band's sound, keyboards, and the future of the band. Speakers: Larry Selman, Mike Swann, Noel Flatt, Karen Bice, Peter Freimanis
    - Frayed Minks interview, 1986-03-28; wrc07527 (Box 21)
      Contents include: Alex Malinin interviews members of Frayed Minks, Robert Estep and Liz Manklin about their music experience, songwriting, recording music, Estep's guitar skills and playing, musical influences, favorite albums, the meaning behind certain songs, and Public News. Speakers: Robert Estep, Liz Manklin, Toby Blunt
    - Texas Music Special 2, 1986-03-29; wrc07528 (Box 21)
      Contents include: (00:01) Living Pieces; (24:13) The Banks; (37:43) The Wolves; (57:43) Frayed Minks; This program features short interviews, history on the bands, and music. Speakers: Robert Estep, Liz Manklin, Toby Blunt, Larry Selman, Mike Swann, Noel Flatt, Karen Bice, Peter Freimanis, Alvin Mullins, Robert Gibbons, Mike Bergeron, Hap Logan, Stu Cannon, Alex Malinin
    - William F. Buckley, Jr. and John Kenneth Galbraith debate, 1986-04-07; wrc07529 (Box 21)
      Contents include: In the Rice Memorial Center's Grand Hall, William F. Buckley, Jr. and John Kenneth Galbraith debate. Ron Stone acts as a moderator and Edward Williams, Allen Matusow, and Alan Grob are panelists. The debaters discuss Pres. Ronald Reagan's economic policy. Speakers: William F. Buckley, John Kenneth Galbraith, Ron Stone, Allen Matusow, Alan Grob, Mike Gladu, Edward Williams
    - Rice Jazz Ensemble, 1986-04-09; wrc08050 (Box 21)
      Contents include: Rice Jazz Ensemble performs in the Grand Hall of the Rice Memorial Center. Speakers: Larry Slezak, Ken Richardson, Robert Harnden, Julie Mayes, Philip Hall, Syd Polk, Eric Furst, Brian Waldecker, Jason Brown, Stephen Carl, Philip Hall, Matt McCarthy, Chris Madland
    - Baseball - Rice vs. University of Texas, 1986-04-12; wrc07961 (Box 21)
      Contents include: Jonathan Sadow and Lyn Michaels call a Rice Owls baseball game against the University of Texas. The final score was Rice 3, University of Texas 10. We deleted radio music at the end of the recording. Speakers: Jonathan Sadow, Lyn Michaels
    - Baseball - Rice vs University of Houston, 1986-04-26; wrc07530 (Box 21)
      Contents include: Jonathan Sadow and Bud Thomas call a Rice Owls baseball game against University of Houston. The final score was Rice 0, University of Houston 7. We deleted radio music at the end of the recording. Speakers: Jonathan Sadow, Bud Thomas
    - Green on Red interview, 1986-05-02; wrc07531 (Box 21)
      Contents include: A KTRU DJ interviews Green on Red members, Chris Cacavas and Chuck Prophet about Houston places, their band name, touring, and recording. Speakers: Chris Cacavas, Chuck Prophet
    - Wilma live, 1986-05-19; wrc07983 (Box 21)
      Contents include: Wilma plays "Pornography Lies," "Georgie Girl," and another song. Speakers: K.D. Davis, Kris Panebianco, Louise Diedrich, Yvette Kay
    - The Pandoras ID, 1986-05; wrc08051 (Box 21)
      Contents include: Members of The Pandoras do a station ID. Speakers: Paula Pierce, Melanie Vammen, Kim Shattuck, Karen Blankfeld
    - S and M - On Waugh Gallery, 1986-06; wrc07990 (Box 21)
      Contents include: On "S and M," a KTRU DJ talks to the On Waugh Gallery owners/employees about the gallery, raising money, upcoming silent auction, large parties, and Saltwater Cats. Speakers: Karen Poltarek, Loretta Cooper, Ted Brown
    - Texas Music Special - The Footnotes, 1986; wrc08015 (Box 21)
      Contents include: Alex Malinin talks about the band The Footnotes and includes live music. Recording ends abruptly. Speakers: Rick Eakens, Alex Malinin, Allan Gill
    - Rice Owls Women's Basketball vs. Baylor University, 1986; wrc08016 (Box 21)
      Contents include: Jonathan Sadow and Lyn Michaels do play-by-play for the Rice women's basketball game vs. Baylor. Recording ends abruptly. Speakers: Jonathan Sadow, Lyn Michaels
    - The Church ID, 1986; wrc08052 (Box 21)
      Contents include: Marty Willson-Piper of The Church does a station ID. Speaker: Marty Willson-Piper
    - They Might Be Giants ID, 1986; wrc08053 (Box 21)
      Contents include: John Flansburgh and John Linnell of the They Might Be Giants do a station ID. Speakers: John Flansburgh, John Linnell
  - Sub-Series: 1986/1987
    - The Kilkenny Cats live, 1986-10-16; wrc07555 (Box 21)
      Contents include: The Kilkenny Cats play live at Willy's Pub. Speakers: Sean O'Brien, Allen Wagner, Clifton Hill, Keith Landers, Tom Cheek
    - Flaming Lips interview, 1986-12; wrc07556 (Box 21)
      Contents include: Sarah Keller interviews Flaming Lips member Wayne Coyne and their manager Michele Vlasimsky about promotions, favorite bands, being a local band, touring, record funding, charts, mass mailing, the band's history, making their first music videos, songwriting, perceptions by Oklahomans, out of state perceptions of being an Oklahoma rock band, and living and playing in economically depressed Oklahoma. Speakers: Wayne Coyne, Michele Vlasimsky, and Sarah Keller
    - Promos, 1986; wrc08084 (Box 21)
      Contents include: DJs perform various promos for T-shirts and KTRU Movie Madness. Speaker: Stan Barber
    - S and M - Elegant Doormats, 1987-01-08; wrc08000 (Box 21)
      Contents include: On "S and M," a KTRU DJ talks to members of the Elegant Doormats about their Houston band and playing in Austin. Speakers: Scott Telles, Leigh Newsom, John Foxworth
    - Chicken Skin Music, part 1, 1987-01-14; wrc08078_01 (Box 21)
      Contents include: (00:01) Mike Mandrell plays live and talks about his work. (31:02) The Banded Geckos play live and talk about their work. Speakers: Mike Mandrell, Evelyne Taylor, Tim Taylor, David John Scribner
    - Chicken Skin Music, part 2, 1987-01-14; wrc08078_02 (Box 21)
      Contents include: (00:01) Banded Geckos live, location unknown. (11:34) Dr. T and the Tuk Tones live. (28:28) Four Bricks Out of Hadrian's Wall live. Speakers: Evelyne Taylor, Tim Taylor, Gary Coover, Kelley Loftus, Bill Galbraith, Vance Whelply
    - Herschel Berry and the Natives live, 1987-01-28; wrc07557 (Box 21)
      Contents include: Herschel Berry and the Natives plays live at Willy's Pub. Speakers: Herschel Berry, Wylie Hudgins, Kenn Cordray, Karl Logan
    - Culturcide live in studio, 1987-02-04; wrc07558 (Box 21)
      Contents include: Culturcide play live and play around in the studio. We deleted comedy skits not created by KTRU. Speakers: Perry Webb, Dan Workman, Raif Armin
    - Pres. Jimmy Carter speech, 1987-02-16; wrc08079 (Box 22)
      Contents include: For the Rice Institute for Policy Analysis, Pres. Jimmy Carter speaks at the Grand Hall in the Rice Memorial Center. In a speech entitled, "Policy and Management in the White House," Pres. Carter talks about how he focused on his goals during his time as president. Speakers: Joe Cooper, Jimmy Carter, Charles Duncan
    - Chicken Skin Music - Preston Reed, 1987-03-04; wrc08065 (Box 22)
      Contents include: On "Chicken Skin Music," Preston Reed plays live and talks about his guitars and "The Road Less Traveled." Speakers: Preston Reed, David John Scribner
    - Preston Reed live, 1987-03-09; wrc08070 (Box 22)
      Contents include: Preston Reed live at Willy's Pub. Speaker: Preston Reed
    - Chicken Skin Music - Sean Walters, 1987-03-11; wrc08067 (Box 22)
      Contents include: On "Chicken Skin Music," Sean Walters plays live and talks about his background. Speakers: Sean Walters, David John Scribner
    - Howard Henry Baker, Jr. speech, 1987-03-26; wrc08068 (Box 22)